[{"answer": "Absolutely, completely out of control.", "docId": "130318pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "Is this just another illustration as this case has already illuminated of social media completely out of control with a certain element of teenagers in America right now?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "That's correct.", "docId": "130318pmt", "aSentId": 58, "question": "These are the threats from the two teenage girls you have in custody now, right?", "qSentId": 57}, {"answer": "Well, one says, \"You ripped my family apart, you made my cousin cry so when I see you, (EXPLETIVE DELETED), it's going to be a homicide.\"", "docId": "130318pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "What did they say that made you arrest them?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "And the next is, \"I'll celebrate by beating the (EXPLETIVE DELETED) out of Jane Doe.\"", "docId": "130318pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "And the next?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "It was -- it was a very emotionally packed moment that occurred in that courtroom where watching this young boy suffer once he realized what the punishment and what had happened at that point.", "docId": "130318pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "Did you feel that was a significant thing?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "Well, she has not at this point forgiven anybody for what she's been through, the terrible ordeal.", "docId": "130318pmt", "aSentId": 100, "question": "Does she feel any sense of forgiveness to these two young men that did this?", "qSentId": 99}, {"answer": "I'm really asking how you're feeling today as the father of a young man who has been convicted of raping a young teenaged girl.", "docId": "130318pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "Can you repeat that question, please, sir?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "Of course I feel a sense of guilt.", "docId": "130318pmt", "aSentId": 123, "question": "Do you feel a sense of guilt, Mr. Richmond, about the fact you were not there for your son as a father for more than a very little period in his life?", "qSentId": 122}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, they had no text messages for Ma'lik.", "docId": "130318pmt", "aSentId": 130, "question": "You must feel a sense of shame, don't you?", "qSentId": 129}, {"answer": "Well, I feel sorry for the young girl.", "docId": "130318pmt", "aSentId": 163, "question": "But I also understand your son has been convicted of a very serious offense in raping a young woman and what I want to ask you is what is your feeling towards that young girl who went through this terrible ordeal and what is your feeling towards her family?", "qSentId": 162}, {"answer": "Well, you have about five different questions there.", "docId": "130318pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "Did you not think that?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "Well, his apology was for the pain that he caused.", "docId": "130318pmt", "aSentId": 193, "question": "Would you have advised your client to apologize for a crime he's always denied committing?", "qSentId": 192}, {"answer": "There will be an appeal.", "docId": "130318pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "Will you be appealing then, in that case?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "130318pmt", "aSentId": 219, "question": "Can you stay for another segment?", "qSentId": 218}, {"answer": "Well, the judge did find that both defendants were delinquent, in other words, that they were guilty of the crime of rape.", "docId": "130318pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "What does it say about Steubenville or indeed, America and teenagers today?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "I think you have to start from a position that the biggest victim here is not your client.", "docId": "130318pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "How do we advance this to a higher level?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "Oh, it's abhorrent.", "docId": "130318pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "-- what is your view of that behavior?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "But it's not really just about the text.", "docId": "130318pmt", "aSentId": 344, "question": "Ma'lik Richmond had one text out of a day full of testimony full of text messages and e-mails and tweets which he had none, okay?", "qSentId": 343}, {"answer": "Where we go from here is we say we acknowledge if a person does something wrong, then we make amends to that person.", "docId": "130318pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "How do we -- where do we go from here?", "qSentId": 347}, {"answer": "I don't believe -- I don't believe he should have to register as a sex offender until he dies.", "docId": "130318pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "Oh, so you're not going to appeal from the judgment of delinquency?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "Well then maybe you ought to think about that -", "docId": "130318pmt", "aSentId": 375, "question": "Either way, would you want to be judged for the rest of your life for something you did at 16?", "qSentId": 374}, {"answer": "Wait, wait, wait.", "docId": "130318pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "Excuse me?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "I was a young girl.", "docId": "130318pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "Did you choose to make adult films?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "ORDS: I was a 15-year-old girl, and I don't need to apologize to you, honey.", "docId": "130318pmt", "aSentId": 390, "question": "Did you choose to make adult films and profit?", "qSentId": 389}, {"answer": "Well, she's saying don't judge someone.", "docId": "130318pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "What is the relevance of that?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "OK, I've got to leave it there.", "docId": "130318pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "I'm not -- did you hear me disagree with that?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "You know, Piers, it's not shocking to me.", "docId": "130318pmt", "aSentId": 435, "question": "What did you make of it?", "qSentId": 434}, {"answer": "I'm glad you asked that.", "docId": "130318pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "Are these just very unusual children that get affected?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "I think with this young man, you had an unbelievable recipe for disaster on so many different fronts.", "docId": "130318pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "It enrages me, to tell you the truth.", "docId": "130318pmt", "aSentId": 484, "question": "But where was she with this seven foot spreadsheet of murderers, with taking him to these gun ranges all the time, feeding this tormented, weird obsessive loner mind?", "qSentId": 483}, {"answer": "I would not like to see her out in society, if you want to know my opinion.", "docId": "130318pmt", "aSentId": 516, "question": "Is she just a cold-blooded psycho killer?", "qSentId": 515}, {"answer": "Well, you know, it all begins with fantasy.", "docId": "130318pmt", "aSentId": 537, "question": "Very quickly, on that, of course the great debate is can somebody who is having these outrageous fantasies, really evil stuff, does that make them a criminal?", "qSentId": 536}, {"answer": "I'm delighted she's done it, for whatever her reason.", "docId": "130318pmt", "aSentId": 557, "question": "But what did you make of her?", "qSentId": 556}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "130318pmt", "aSentId": 593, "question": "And why don't you just talk me through what you believe caused the tragic death of this young girl?", "qSentId": 592}, {"answer": "Yeah, she's been under a lot of stress.", "docId": "130318pmt", "aSentId": 633, "question": "Just from that point of view, has she been suffering since the death of Cous-Cous?", "qSentId": 632}, {"answer": "Well, I think this gives just a powerful example of really how powerful these creatures are.", "docId": "130318pmt", "aSentId": 649, "question": "Would you say that?", "qSentId": 648}]